{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Calculus Terms",
      "firstCardName": "first card name",
      "tags": ["math", "calculus"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Physics Terms",
      "firstCardName": "first card name",
      "tags": ["physics", "classical physics"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "title": "Trig Identities",
      "firstCardName": "first card name",
      "tags": ["math", "trigonometry"]
    },
    {
      "title": "Coding 6",
      "tags": ["test tag 1", "test tag 2"],
      "firstCardName": "first card name",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Derivative",
      "back": "Slope of a curve at a point",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "Integral",
      "back": "Area of under a curve",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "Kinematics",
      "back": "Study of the 'how' of motion",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "front": "bruh edit",
      "back": "fr",
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "front": "Pythagorean Identity",
      "back": "* some identity image",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "test front",
      "back": "test back\n",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "test front 2",
      "back": "test back\n",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "test front 3",
      "back": "test back\n",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "test front 4",
      "back": "test back\n",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "front 2",
      "back": "back 2",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "Double Angle Identites",
      "back": "** some image",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "Limit",
      "back": "some def",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 9
    }
  ]
}
